<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Duckhunt - A Discord Bot</title>
    <link>https://duckhunt.me/en/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Duckhunt - A Discord Bot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://duckhunt.me/en/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bot Settings</title>
      <link>https://duckhunt.me/en/page/bot-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duckhunt.me/en/page/bot-settings/</guid>
      <description>To set a setting, use dh!settings set &amp;lt;parameter&amp;gt; &amp;lt;value&amp;gt;
You can view modified settings by using dh!settings modified
For resetting a setting to its default value, use dh!settings reset &amp;lt;parameter&amp;gt;
   Parameter Type Default value Comment     announce_level_up bool True Toggle the level up/down announcements   bang_lag float 0.5 Time in seconds between a hunter&amp;rsquo;s shot and what happens. This can be disabled by setting it to 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Command list</title>
      <link>https://duckhunt.me/en/page/command-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duckhunt.me/en/page/command-list/</guid>
      <description>All commands are written with the universal dh! prefix.
Alternatively, you can use the prefix set on your server too, (the default is !) which can be changed by server owners.
Arguments to the commands listed below are specified with &amp;lt;&amp;gt; if they must be specified, and with [] otherwise. Please don’t type the brackets on commands, thanks :)
You can pass a player as an argument using his/her User ID, a mention, their nickname, or their username and Discord tag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://duckhunt.me/en/page/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duckhunt.me/en/page/faq/</guid>
      <description>How do I play? Playing DuckHunt is easy. When a duck (a message sent by the bot looking like 🦆 &amp;lt; COUAAC) appears in the channel, use the dh!bang command to kill it. You can reload your weapon with dh!reload when you have no more bullets in your current clip.
You can also access the shop using dh!shop [name of the item you want] to buy objects you&amp;rsquo;ll need in your hunting career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Duckhunt</title>
      <link>https://duckhunt.me/en/page/install-the-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duckhunt.me/en/page/install-the-bot/</guid>
      <description>First, I’d like to thank HostMyServers for providing me a server to host DuckHunt on. It is fast, reliable and well-supported!
Adding the official bot to your server is super easy ! Follow the instructions:
 Join our discord server to get support if needed. You can ask a @Moderator to get the @Server Owner role, reserved for admins of DuckHunt on their servers! Invite the bot to your server by clicking here In the channel you want to use, type !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shop Items</title>
      <link>https://duckhunt.me/en/page/shop-items/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://duckhunt.me/en/page/shop-items/</guid>
      <description>You can buy objects with the command dh!shop [item number] [possible arguments, such as the @target nickname] You need to have enough exp to buy an item.
   Shop ID Item name Description Exp cost     1 Extra bullet One bullet is added directly into the gun chamber. 7   2 Extra clip One clip is added to your stock. 13   3 AP ammo (antiblindage) Damage x2 for 24h.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>